# https://opentdb.com/api_config.php
question_data = [{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Rapper Snoop Dogg&#039;s real name is &#039;Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.&#039;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Soulja Boy&#039;s &#039;Crank That&#039; won a Grammy for Best Rap Song in 2007.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The cover of The Beatles album &quot;Abbey Road&quot; featured a Volkswagen Beetle in the background.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Norwegian producer Kygo released a remix of the song &quot;Sexual Healing&quot; by Marvin Gaye.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Ashley Frangipane performs under the stage name Halsey.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Twenty One Pilots&quot; made the song &quot;The Motion&quot; featuring Sampha.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Nick Mason is the only member to appear on every Pink Floyd album.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Green Day&#039;s album &#039;American Idiot&#039; is considered a &quot;punk rock opera.&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]